globalforexincome.net 2010-11-22

# Global Forex Income : Think Globally - Trade Globally

This **privacy policy** will elaborate on how we use personal information submitted at [**GlobalForexIncome.net**](http://www.globalforexincome.net/) website. We request you to read this privacy policy before using GlobalForexIncome.net site or submitting any personal information. However when you use this site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. Although our privacy policy may be changed in the future to keep in tune with the growing requirements of our website, these changes if any will be posted wherever applicable. Nevertheless if any changes are made to this privacy policy, it will only be applicable to activities and information on a going forward basis and will not have any retrospective effect.

We earnestly request you to review our privacy policy whenever you visit our website to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

**  
Collection of Information**

GlobalForexIncome.net collects email addresses and other personal information only when voluntarily submitted by our visitors, as for registration on our website. This information you provide is used to cater to your own specific requests. We do not part with this information to any third party unless required by law to do so. 

**  
Cookies**

If and when GlobalForexIncome.net uses cookies and tracking technology, it is only restricted to ascertaining browser type and operating systems of the visitors to the site and for tracking the number of visitors to GlobalForexIncome.net. This is to understand how visitors could be using our site, so that we could customize our site to appropriately cater to our visitor's needs. But such cookies will not be used in anyway whatsoever to gather personal information of the visitors to the GlobalForexIncome.net site. You have our unflinching commitment on this vital aspect. 

**  
Distribution of Information**

GlobalForexIncome.net may share information with investigating agencies, government departments or other entities engaged in fraud prevention or investigation. GlobalForexIncome.net may do this only when permitted or required by law, or in the course of trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions. GlobalForexIncome.net will not provide your personal information email addresses etc to any company whatsoever for marketing or sales purposes. 

**  
Security of data collected**

Please rest assured that any email address or personal information submitted at GlobalForexIncome.net website is kept absolutely secure. Only our authorized employees who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential have access to this information. 

**  
Privacy Contact Information**

In case you have any questions, queries, doubts or comments about our privacy policy we urge you to contact us by email through the **Customer support** section.
